# **Dana Shem-Toy**

Phone number: 0503794444 | Email: sdana1933@gmail.com | Birth date: 21/12/1996

## **Personal Profile**

Unit **8200**, I.D.F Graduate after 2 years of mandatory service, I am a second year software engineering student with a **GPA of 90**, with a healthy appetite for knowledge and a passion for software development. during my military service I was responsible for the operation of real-time production application environments, passing on knowledge to new recruits, maintaining my team's knowledge base.

I am a quick learner, able to understand complex systems, technical oriented, excellent human relations, I take responsibility, able to multitask and work under pressure, team player, self organizing.

# Work Experience

Researcher at Israel M.O.D [ 2019 - 2019 ]

- Job description details cannot be shared.
- A high level of security clearance.

## System Operator at I.D.F Intelligence Unit '8200' [2016 - 2018]

- Production software maintenance specialist
- Software real-time performance research and benchmarking
- Physical and Virtual server deployment and maintenance
- Worked and developed with python as main scripting & programming language
- Developed automation tools for infrastructure health checking and end-to-end application testing
- Worked with Microsoft SQL Server
- Software errors troubleshooting
- Working in different operating system environments such as Windows and Linux
- Was in charge of my team's self-managed Mediawiki as knowledge base
- Writing operating procedures

### Education

#### **Academic studies:**

Software Engineering student, Shenkar college [2019-present]

Electronics and computers Certified technician, Ort Holon college [2014-2015].

High School studies in the subjects of electronics and computers, Ort Holon High School [2012-2015]. Knowledge in c and python programming languages.

### Certifications:

2019: Computer network course - Ministry of Defense.

2018: Python course - 'She Codes;' organization.

2017: Web course - 'She Codes;' organization.

2016: 'Sigma' Course -Computer networks and RF training for 8200 unit.

Languages: Hebrew, English.